Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject Files: Trip to China and Tibet, 1977; 9 (Box 1579)
    - Lowell Thomas walking with the children at the Tibetan Refugee Nursery, 10
    - Note: Tibetan Refugee Nursery, Dharamsala, 11
    - Lowell Thomas speaking with two women at the Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 12
    - Children at the Tibetan Refugee Nursery, Dharamsala, 13
    - Lowell Thomas with the caregivers (?) at the Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 14
    - Lowell Thomas speaking with a man at the Tibetan Refugee Nursery, Dharamsala, 15
    - Lowell Thomas speaking with a man at the Tibetan Refugee Nursery, Dharamsala, 16
    - Note: Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 17
    - Lowell Thomas speaking with two women at the Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 18
    - Lowell Thomas with the caregivers (?) at the Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 19
    - Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 20
    - Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 21
    - Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 22
    - Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 23
    - Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 24
    - Tibetan Children in Nursery, Dharamsala, 25
    - Tibetan Refugee Nursery, Dharamsala, 26
    - Note: Mountains, Dharamsala, 27
    - Lowell Thomas speaking with a man in Dharamsala, 28
    - Lowell Thomas looking at the mountains, Dharamsala, India., 29
    - Mountains, Dharamsala, 30
    - Lowell Thomas speaking with a man in front of mountains, Dharamsala, 31
    - Mountains, Dharamsala, 32
    - Lowell Thomas's car driving to wards the mountains, Dharamsala, 33
    - Note: Tibet B/W neg. 2nd Trip, 34
    - Lowell Thomas standing with a man in Dharamsala, 35
    - Lowell Thomas outside of the American Embassy in New Delhi, 36
    - Lowell Thomas and others at the American Embassy, New Delhi, 37
  - Subject Files: Senator Tydings and Admiral Halsey, undated; 10 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Senator Tydings, and Admiral Halsey(?) on a ship with a group of men ], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas, Senator Tydings, and Admiral Halsey(?) on a ship with a group of men], 2
  - Subject files: Max Valentiner, undated; 11 (Box 1579)
    - [Two sailors sitting], 1
    - [A group photo of eight sailors], 2
    - [Two traditional chinese ships (?)], 3
    - [A group photo of eight sailors], 4
  - Subject files: Bertha Spafford Vester, 1965; 12 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Bertha Spafford Vester and another woman (?)], 1
    - [Bertha Spafford Vester and a woman arranging flowers outside], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a woman], 3
    - [Bertha Spafford Vester playing with a dog (?)], 4
    - [Bertha Spafford Vester(?)], 5
    - [Bertha Spafford Vester(?)], 6
    - [Bertha Spafford Vester(?)], 7
    - [Bertha Spafford Vester], 8
  - Subject files: Paula von Hellens, circa 1966 - 1967; 13 (Box 1579)
    - [Paula von Hellens (?)], 1
  - Subject files: Count Felix Von Luckner, undated; 14 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Count Felix Von Luckner (?)], 1
    - [A man holding a fox (?) with two men and a women standing with him], 2
    - Note: I(?) Countess Luckner, Count Luckner, Remarks Sherm Shalley and Fred(?) Ward Holding fox, 3
  - Subject files: Count Felix Von Luckner and Lowell Thomas, Jr., undated; 15 (Box 1579)
    - [Fred Ward (?) holding an animal with Count Luckner, Countess Luckner, and child Sonny standing by], 1
    - Note: I (?) Count Luckner, Fred Ward, Countess Luckner and Sonny at the fur farm, 2
  - Subject files: Mrs. Frieda Ward-Jerusalem, circa 1968; 16 (Box 1579)
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 1
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 2
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 3
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 4
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 5
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 6
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 7
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 8
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 9
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 10
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 11
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 12
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 13
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 14
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 15
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 16
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 17
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 18
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 19
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 20
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 21
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 22
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 23
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 24
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 25
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 26
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 27
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 28
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 29
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 30
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 31
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 32
    - Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 33
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 34
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 35
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 36
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 37
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 38
    - [Mrs. Frieda Ward(?), Jerusalem(?)], 39
  - Subject files: Waterfall, undated; 17 (Box 1579)
    - [Photo of a Waterfall], 1
    - [Photo of a Waterfall], 2
  - Subject files: Western Union telegrams (266,000 received by Lowell Thomas), 1934; 18 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) sitting on top of Wester Union boxes with 2 other men], 1
  - Subject files: Jim Whittaker, circa 1960s; 19 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other people posing next to a airplane], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other people posing next to an aiplane(appears to be a higher definition version of the previous photo)], 2
  - Subject files: Sir Hubert Wilkins, undated; 20 (Box 1579)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Sir Hubert Wilkins (?) looking at photos on a wall], 1
    - Note: Australian, 2
  - Subject files: Sir Hubert Wilkins (photographs for use in Arctic Knight: Sir Hubert Wilkins by Lowell Thomas), circa late 1950s - 1960s; 21 (Box 1579)
    - Note: Dear Mr. Thomas: In going through our production files, we found the enclosed negatives and photographs, 1
    - [Man looking at plane surrounded by a group of people], 2
    - [Blackburn Kangaroo Plane (?) on the side of a hill with three men on top and one standing next to it], 3
    - [A plane sitting in the water surrounded by metals barrells, 4 men are on shore and 1 man is sticking out of the plane], 4
    - [Aerial view of snow-capped arctic mountains], 5
    - [Two men at a campsite], 6
    - [Men sitting outside of a train], 7
    - [Men standing on a submarine [?] in the Arctic], 8
    - [Two men talking], 9
    - [A woman and two men], 10
    - [Soldiers in the trenches], 11
    - [Airplane in front of a glacier], 12
    - [Crowd waving on a ship], 13
    - [Man standing on a ship], 14
    - [Woman and two men on a mountain, valley and building in the background], 15
    - [Man with a film projector, native Eskimos [?] sitting], 16
    - [Men building an igloo], 17
    - [Men in a hot air balloon], 18
    - [Group of men], 19
    - [Men standing on a submarine [?] in the Arctic], 20
    - [Men standing on a submarine [?] in the Arctic], 21
    - [Men sitting outside tents], 22
    - [Four men on a ship], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing a fur coat], 24
  Box 1580
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Sir Hubert Wilkins and Bernt Balchen (High Adventure with Lowell Thomas television series), 1957 December; 1 (Box 1580)
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men with the Explorer's Club flag in front of an airplane], 1
    - Note [CBS; Arctic Pioneers on "High Adventure" Dec. 23], 2
    - Note [CBS; Lowell Thomas Hits Arctic Trail], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men with the Explorer's Club flag], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man sitting by a seld], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other men looking at a map], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men looking at a map], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and three others with the Explorer's Club flag], 8
  - Subject files: Winter Sports Carnival at Lake Placid, undated; 2 (Box 1580)
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman dressed at a king and queen], 1
  - Subject files: Woman (negative found in French diary), 1917; 3 (Box 1580)
    - [Woman outside of a brick house], 1
    - [Woman standing by stone staircase], 2
  - Subject files: Admiral John Lorimer Warden, undated; 4 (Box 1580)
    - [Portrait of Admiral John Lorimer Warden], 1
  - Subject files: World War I, circa 1917 - 1918; 5 (Box 1580)
    - [World War I soldiers], 1
    - [World War I soldiers in the street], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a soldier during World War I], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man and his dog during World War I], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas with pointed campaign hat, in rear seat, accompanied by his assistants en route to the Italian front. In middle Gen. [General] Webb Hayes, son of U.S. Pres. [President] Ritherford B. Hayes; on right in rear seat Col. [Colonel] Pierro Tozzi, Italisn staff officer.], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with three other soldiers during World War I; "To Lowell Thomas in rememberance of Venice 1918"], 6
    - [A crowd of people with World War I soldiers], 7
    - [Painting of a man on the back of a camel], 8
  - Subject files: World War I (Arabia, Egypt, Palestine), 1918; 6 (Box 1580)
    - [Rocks by the ocean], 1
    - [Man floating in the ocean while reading a book and holding an umbrella], 2
    - [Three World War I soldiers looking at documents], 3
    - [Men with dogs outside of a tent during World War I], 4
    - [World War I soldier standing with an Arabian [?] man], 5
    - [Two men with camels], 6
    - [Two men standing outside of a tent], 7
    - [T.E. Lawrence [?] standing on a balcony], 8
    - [T.E. Lawrence [?] and others standing on a staircase], 9
    - [Group of men in Palestine [?]], 10
    - [T.E. Lawrence [?] and two men talking in Palestine [?]], 11
    - [Sailboat on the ocean], 12
    - [Man in Arab [?] clothing], 13
    - [Aerial view of man and two camels leaving a small village [?]], 14
    - [Map of Arabia; The war in the land of the Arabian Nights commenced at the holy city of Mecca after which Emir Feisal and Colonel Lawrence led the Arab army while it fought its way north across the desert for over a thousand miles to Aleppo. Dotted line indicated the region covered by this narrative.], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas and a General [General]], 16
    - [Portrait of a man], 17
    - [Man with a gun on horseback], 18
    - [Man], 19
    - [T.E. Lawrence], 20
    - [World War I soldier], 21
    - [World War I soldier standing with a woman], 22
    - [T.E. Lawrence], 23
    - [T.E. Lawrence], 24
    - [Man drinking from a river in a canyon], 25
    - [Collapsed railroad [?] bridge], 26
    - [Line of soldiers on horseback], 27
    - [Men on camels], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas on a camel], 29
    - [Sandstorm englufing a town], 30
    - [Two soldiers by a small pond], 31
    - [Men sitting on camels], 32
    - [Large crowd of people in the city of Mecca, Saudi Arabia], 33
    - [Lowell Thomas with other soldiers during World War I], 34
  - Subject files: World War I (Arabia, Egypt, Palestine), 1918; 7 (Box 1580)
    - [Man bathing in a pool of water], 1
    - [Man on horseback, child standing with gun], 2
    - [Man coughing], 3
    - [Man on camel next to a makeshift tank [?]], 4
    - [Three men on camels in the desert], 5
    - [Group of men on a ship], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas with his camera in an airplane], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and T.E. Lawrence], 8
    - [T.E. Lawrence and Lowell Thomas], 9
  - Subject files: World War I (Lowell Thomas indexed photographs), 1918; 8 (Box 1580)
    - [Ship docked in port], 1
    - [Man standing standing on a ship, looking at land], 2
    - [Group of men crowing around something], 3
    - [T.E. Lawrence sitting in white robes], 4
    - [T.E. Lawrence standing in white robes], 5
    - [T.E. Lawrence sitting in white robes], 6
    - [Man on horseback surrounded by people], 7
    - [Man and woman speaking, others in background], 8
    - [Arabian [?] soldiers], 9
    - [Ancient ruins of Petra; Urn Tomb], 10
    - [Ruins of Petra], 11
    - [Ruins of Petra], 12
    - [Man on horse surrounded by people in front of a tent], 13
    - [Ruins at Petra], 14
    - [Child's silhouette in a doorwat at the ruins of Petra [?]], 15
    - [Man standing outside of a doorway at Petra], 16
    - [Ruins at Petra], 17
    - [Group of men eating at Petra], 18
    - [Ruins at petra], 19
    - [Soldier picking flowers], 20
    - [Ruins at Petra [?]], 21
    - [Middle Eastern soldiers sitting on stone steps], 22
    - [Two Middle Eastern soldiers by a small pond], 23
    - [Two men examining ruins], 24
    - [Stone monument ruins], 25
    - [Soldier standing in front of mountains], 26
    - [Soldier standing before mountains], 27
    - [Men examining a stone structure], 28
    - [Group of men sitting on the side of a cliff], 29
    - [Campsite], 30
    - [Group of men at their camp], 31
    - [Man serving food to a crowd], 32
    - [Two people observing a building on top of a mountain], 33
  - Subject files: World War II, circa 1940s; 9 (Box 1580)
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other soldiers during World War II], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of young soldiers during World War II], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a pilot in front of an airplane; World War II], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a pilot in front of an Army Air Force plane during World War II], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a pilot; World War II], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with officers during World War II], 6
  - Subject files: World War II (Lowell Thomas, Chiang Kai-shek and General Albert C. Wedemeyer), circa 1940s; 10 (Box 1580)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with Chiang Kai-shek and General Albert C. Wedemeyer], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with Chiang Kai-shek and General Albert C. Wedemeyer], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with Chiang Kai-shek and General Albert C. Wedemeyer], 3
  - Subject files: Harrison Forman and Chairman Mao Tse-Tung [Zedong], 1944; 11 (Box 1580)
    - [Harrison Foreman and Chairman Mao Tse-Tung [Zedong]], 1
  - Subject files: World War II (Lowell Thomas and General George S. Patton), circa 1940s; 12 (Box 1580)
    - [Lowell Thomas and General George S. Oatton with two other officers], 1
  - Subject files: Miscellaneous photographs, undated; 13 (Box 1580)
    - Winston Pote (Photographer) [Photographers on a snowy mountain], 1
    - Winston Pote (Photographer) [People skiing], 2
    - Winston Pote (Photographer) [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. on skis], 3
    - [Living room with fireplace], 4
    - [Staircase in house], 5
    - [Man and woman kissing], 6
    - [Fireplace in a house], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with a man and a woman], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas outside, standing next to a bust], 9
    - [Smiling man], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas at a banquet event], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men looking at a photograph], 12
    - [Man with a dog], 13
    - [Group of men and women], 14
    - [Two men talking], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men], 16
    - [Young soldier], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas crowning a woman], 18
    - [Group of men on a fake horse and carriage], 19
    - Note: Electra: What is the name of the gentleman with President Huegli and LT?, 20
    - Note: LT in NY Cap. Cities office. Behind "Lawrence" given to Holy Land Soc. This is your life + globe. Now at Kane[?], 21
    - Note: L.T. + Sascha Siemel. So Amer. Explorer, Also - with Gen. Robt. Lee Bullard, 22
    - Note: No. 2 U.S. general in WWI, 23
  - Subject files: Miscellaneous photographs, undated; 14 (Box 1580)
    - [Group of men standing around a crashed airplane], 1
    - [Men working on a wooden wall [?]], 2
    - [City Skyline], 3
    - [Side of Clover Brook in the winter], 4
    - [Side of Clover Brook], 5
    - [Side of Clover Brook in the winter], 6
    - [Child playing in the grass, farm in the background], 7
    - [Farm house], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas with Thomas Dewey and unidentified man], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and three men looking at a map], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and four others standing under the sign for Lowell Street], 11
    - [Group of men looking at blueprints [?] under the Forum], 12
    - [Camera team filming natives in canoes [?]], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man with a gun at the Afghan border], 14
    - [Men on camels], 15
    - [Young Lowell Thomas], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas writing in a journal at his campsite in Malta [?]], 17
    - [Filming on a snowy hill], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man by ruins], 19
    - [Two men looking at a building on a mountain], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas inspecting a broken tank], 21
    - [Sign announcing "With Allenby in Palestine surpassed by 'Through Romantic India' with Lowell Thomas"], 22
    - [Two soldiers in the trenches], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thoms Jr. playing hockey], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr [?], and two other men talking], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas being filmed], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to a man with a cane], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. doing a broadcast by candle light [?] *This photo is backwards*], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a broadcast with two natives], 29
    - [The Shenandoah Valley Motel, where Lowell Thomas showered on June 1st, 1934], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas broadcasting on NBC], 31
    - [Pepsi-Cola sign in Greenville, birthplace of Lowell Thomas], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas with his camera in the back of a plane], 33
    - [Lowell Thomas writing on a typewriter], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man on top of a mountain], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas and T.E. Lawrence], 36
    - [Sign: The boyhood home of Lowell Thomas (turn left next block)], 37
    - [Lowell Thomas photographing the Dalai Lama], 38
    - [Lowell Thomas holding his skis on top of a mountain], 39
    - [Lowell Thomas with an officer], 40
    - [Two men looking through Cinerama film footage], 41
    - [Lowell Thomas broadcasting with his dog], 42
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. with other members of the Explorer's Club], 43
    - [Portrait of a baby [Lowell Thomas?]], 44
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group at the stock exchange [?]], 45
    - [Two people on a dirt road], 46
    - [Two people on a dirt road], 47
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with an elderly man], 48
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with an elderly man], 49
    - [Bertha Spafford Vester standing with a woman in a veil], 50
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas in a boat], 51
    - [Lowell Thomas in sunglasses and a hat], 52
    - [Lowell Thomas and others on a film set [?]], 53
    - [Lowell Thomas behind a microphone, "Columbia"], 54
    - [Lowell Thomas standing on rocks and pointing], 55
  Box 1581
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [softball], circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1581)
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man and woman at a softball game], 1
    - [Man blowing his nose at a softball game], 2
    - [Blurry photo of softball field [?]], 3
    - [Woman in the crowd, enjoying the softball game], 4
    - [Man taking a photograph at a softball game], 5
    - [Marching band at a softball game], 6
    - [Young boy at a softball game], 7
    - [Young lady in the crowd at a softball game], 8
    - [Man covering his mouth at a softball game], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas at a softball game], 10
    - [Man in costume at a softball game], 11
    - [Man in costume at a softball game], 12
    - [Two men at a softball game], 13
    - [Young lady at a softball game], 14
    - [Softball player on the field], 15
    - [Softball player holding a bat], 16
    - [Man holding a camera at a softball game], 17
    - [Umpire at the softball game], 18
    - [Man batting at softball game], 19
    - [Crowd watching softball game], 20
    - [Outfield softball player, uniform: "Saints and Sinners"], 21
    - [Woman in the crowd at a softball game], 22
    - [Men talking at softball game], 23
    - [Man watching softball game through a fence], 24
    - [Man dressed as a cop walking out onto the softball field], 25
    - [Man dressed as a clown with members of the Saints and Sinners softball team behind him], 26
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 27
    - [Softball team lining up at home plate], 28
    - [Francis Ryan Thomas [?] watching the softball game with other spectators], 29
    - [Spectator taking a photograph at a softball game], 30
    - [Man in costume at a softball game], 31
    - [Man in overalls at a softball game], 32
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 33
    - [Looking through the fence at a softball game], 34
    - [Farm behind the softball field [?] Quaker Hill [?]], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas and others at a softball game], 36
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [softball], circa 1930s; 2 (Box 1581)
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 1
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 2
    - [Spectators at a softball game], 3
    - [Woman watching the softball game], 4
    - [Woman taking pictures at the softball game], 5
    - [Saints and Sinners player batting at a softball game], 6
    - [Softball spectators and band], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with fellow softball players and spectators], 8
    - [Woman drinking at softball game], 9
    - [Spectators at a softball game including Lowell Thomas in overalls], 10
    - [Spectators at a softball game including Lowell Thomas in overalls], 11
    - [Man and two women on a porch], 12
    - [Man smoking on the porch], 13
    - [Man smoking on the porch], 14
    - [Man and woman sitting on porch steps], 15
    - [Man and woman sitting on front steps of a house], 16
    - [Man and woman sitting on front steps of a house], 17
    - [People gathered on the front porch of a house], 18
    - [Woman with a Mickey Mouse balloon on the softball field], 19
    - [Woman with a Mickey Mouse balloon with a man on the softball field], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas enjoying a Coke at a softball game], 21
    - [Woman being carried off the softball field], 22
    - [The Saints and Sinners softball team and a pep band], 23
    - [Member of the Saints and Sinners softball team], 24
    - [Member of the Saints and Sinners softball team], 25
    - [Woman in the crowd holding her nose at a softball game], 26
    - [Softball player in the field], 27
    - [Softball player in the field], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas pitching at a softball game], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas pitching at a softball game], 30
    - [Softball team member running], 31
    - [Softball player running into home base], 32
    - [Softball player [Nine Old Men?]], 33
    - [Crowd at a softball game], 34
    - [Spectators at the softball game], 35
  - Subject files: 35 millimeter negative roll [softball], circa 1930s; 3 (Box 1581)
    - [Painters [?] softball team], 1
    - [Woman taking to man at a softball game, marching band in the background], 2
    - [Man getting bandaged up [in costume?] at softball game], 3
    - [Man at softball game], 4
    - [Man at softball game], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas at softball game], 6
    - [Woman baking cookies], 7
    - [Two men talking at softball game], 8
    - [Spectators at softball game], 9
    - [Members of Painters [?] softball team], 10
    - [Painters [?] softball player], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with someone at a softball game], 12
    - [Softball player at softball game], 13
    - [Softball players at game], 14
    - [Little girl watching softball game], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a woman at a softball game], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman at a softball game], 17